Hello friends, welcome to our
YouTube channel Aryan Automotive. So
friends, today we have TVS Antarq 125. By looking at the
thumbnail, you must have understood what has
happened to the vehicle. So friends, it has been
attacked by a rat, that is, the
rat has cut its entire wiring.
As you can see from here,
the entire wiring etc. has been cut and you can
see it from here and you
can also see it from here. You must be seeing the trace of the rat.
So in this video we
will open the complete scooter and we will learn how to install the wiring.
So in this video we are going to install the complete new wiring.
So let's
start the video. If you are new to the channel, then
please subscribe to the channel and like and share the video.
[Music]
[Prasha]
So friends, we have
completely opened the scooter and you can see
what the rat has done from here. It has completely damaged
all the wiring.
Its wiring has also been repaired very badly.  You
can see it
complete here once or twice, it has been completely parted in it, you
can see the oil section here completely,
we will install new wiring in it
and whatever coupler of ours, meter etc. is
damaged, we will repair it and
install it in it, if it is not completed then
friends we have
ordered the complete wiring for it, you can see it
is absolutely new
and it is
made of Minda,
we have ordered something of this type from the company itself,
so let's clean it and fit it quickly
and show you how to start the bike,
so let's start
[Music]
So friends we have completed the whole thing,
whatever coupler was broken on the bike, we have
prepared it by folding the cloth, let's
install the new wiring,
so like this
[Music] you have to
lock it and go, it will sit like this while coming from the door
[Music]
[Music] A A [Music] [Music
]
A A
[Music] [Music] [
Praise] [Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]
So friends, our wedding is complete,
we have
installed all the couples properly, you can see,
we have also installed the battery etc., the
relay from here, everything is complete, in this
way we have done some wiring for
it, so
now let's turn it on and start it, you
can see that our scooter has turned on
[Music] you
can see it is working
properly
[Music] [Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music
]
[Music]
So friends, our scooter is complete [Music] you
can see it is starting properly, let's
check the headlight from the door [Music] the
indicator is working properly, the
tail light from the back is also working
[Music]
so the bike is almost complete and it is very
good or if
you already have any problem related to any two wheeler, then
you can comment us
so that we can make a video on it, so do
tell us in the comment box how you liked the video,
also do subscribe to our channel, so that's all for
this video
See you in a new video with a new
topic, ok thank you.